

Brian Moreira, 30 years old hey@brianmoreira.com +55 (21) 9 2020-8221 Teresópolis, Rio de Janeiro - Brazil

brianmoreira.com/en/

Hello!

My name is Brian. I graduated in Graphic Design and worked as web designer, front-end developer, user interface (UI) and user experience (UX) designer, as well as graphic designer for marketing teams.

Languages: English, portuguese.

Softwares: Toon Boom Harmony, Figma, Adobe: Photoshop, Premiere, After Effects, XD.

Experience

Graphic Designer | D360 Digital Marketing

Place: Remote | Period: 2023 - 2024

More than 80 Instagram posts designed for the D360 agency, along with landing pages layouts, websites, banners and outdoors.

UI/UX Designer | Fintera

Place: Remoto | Period: 2020 - 2023

At Fintera, I've worked for three years as an UI/UX designer, creating high-fidelity interactive prototypes on Figma, drawing new screens and updating existing ones in their system.

Besides developing improvements on their existing modules, I was responsible for designing a new module from scratch. In it, I designed dashboards, filters, lists, labels, pages and created a component for automatic verification of bank reconciliations.

Designer & Front-End | Nexaas

Place: Rio de Janeiro - São Paulo | Period: 2015 - 2019

At Nexaas, for the most part as part of the marketing team, responsible for updating all of the company's product's websites. Relocated from the Rio office to the, at the time, new office in São Paulo in the beginning of 2019.

Web Designer | DeBra Tecnologia

Place: Teresópolis Period: 2012 - 2014 Web Designer | Shopp Mídia

Place: Teresópolis Period: 2010 - 2012

Education

Graphic Design | Higher Education

Universidade Estácio de Sá - Rio de Janeiro, RJ Period: 2014 - 2017

Courses

English

lebeu / Progresso Teresópolis 2008 - 2013

Drawing I

Quanta Academia de Artes São Paulo - EAD 2020 - 2021

Advanced Animation

Anima Mundi / Cesar Coelho Rio de Janeiro 2018 (Workload of 36 hours)

Cinematic Form and Style

Cinema em Cena / Pablo Villaça Rio de Janeiro 2017 (Workload of 15 hours)

Computer Graphics

Seven Computação Gráfica Rio de Janeiro 2013 - 2014

Basic Drawing

Impacto Quadrinhos Rio de Janeiro 2012 - 2013

Basic Animation Workshop

Anima Mundi / Aída Queiroz Rio de Janeiro 2018 (Workload of 30 hours)

Theory, Language and Criticism

Cinema em Cena / Pablo Villaça Rio de Janeiro 2014 (Workload of 15 hours)